

# Supriya Sudhir Digital Marketing Executive

+971 552099764 supriyasudir@gmail.com supriya101.github.io/portfolio/ Dubai, UAE

#### SUMMARY

Dedicated Digital marketing professional with over 5+ years of experience in creating WordPress websites, generating quality leads through online advertisements and creating engaging content across major social platforms. Having a strong background in SEO, including keyword research and on-page/off-page strategies, to grow web traffic organically on search engines. Additionally having a technical background in web development with knowledge of HTML and CSS. Looking to apply my skills and passion to drive growth in a dynamic digital marketing role.

#### EXPERIENCE

04/2023 - 11/2024

## **Digital Marketing Specialist/Web Designers**

London American City College, UAE 7

- The website lacc.ae, londonamericancitycollege.com & other lacc websites have been redesigned to be more user-friendly on all platforms.
- Online advertising Google Ads & Facebook campaigns are managed & generated quality leads.
   Created engaging content, infographics, & reels for social media platforms for Facebook,
   Instagram, LinkedIn & YouTube to promote the college's brand.
- Using keyword research(SemRush), on-page and off-page SEO strategies are optimized for the college's website to improve visibility and organic traffic on search engines.

08/2023 - 09/2023

## **Amazon Associate Freelancer (E-commerce)**

Skyfield Agritech, UAE ↗

- Created product listings on Amazon, which involved providing detailed and accurate product information.
- Optimized product titles, descriptions, and images to enhance visibility and appeal to potential customers.
- Ensured that all product listings comply with Amazon's guidelines and policies.
- Implemented SEO strategies to boost a product's position at 1st position in the Amazon search results.

12/2020 - 03/2023

## **SEO** Associate

Firstcry.Com, Pune 7

- Developed an article blueprint for a Firstcry Parenting Website, offering expert guidance for parents.
- Created engaging and informative content across various parenting topics, including newborn essentials, baby development milestones, breastfeeding, sleep training, nutrition, and child safety.
- Conducted keyword research(SEMrush) and implemented strategic SEO techniques to optimize content for search engine visibility.

03/2022 - 10/2022

## Website Developer and SMO

CPI Mallikarjun School, Goa 7

- Created the UI design for the CPI Mallikarjun School website, focusing on creating an engaging and user-friendly interface for the school's online presence.
- Developed and managed social media content for the CPImallikarjun website.
- Used best SEO techniques to increase visibility in search results.

06/2020 - 11/2020

#### **Digital Marketing Intern**

Clariwell Global Services Institute, Pune 7

- Worked with the SEO team on projects involving On-Page and Off-Page optimization for client websites.
- Worked with social media optimisation by posting posters on client websites.
- Extra skills learned: Email Marketing, Google Analytics, Keyword Research, Keyword Optimisation & Link Building.

10/2019 - 05/2020

#### **UI/UX Developer**

- Successfully designed and implemented a user-friendly and responsive UI for the Konfhub platform.
- Collaborated closely with cross-functional teams to understand user requirements and translate them into visually appealing design solutions.
- Prototyping tools (Figma, Sketch), Usability testing tools, Responsive design frameworks.

## EDUCATION

05/2016 - 05/2019

**Computer Science** 

Bangalore University - Jyoti Nivas College Autonomous

Master of Computer Applications (MCA)

04/2013 - 04/2016

**Computer Science** 

Goa University - Shree Damodar College Of Commerce & Economics

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA)

# CERTIFICATES

03/2020 - 11/2020

Web Development & Digital Marketing (SEO, SMM, WordPress and Google Ads) Certification

Clariwell Global Services Institute, Pune

# SKILLS

Facebook Ads & Instagram

Ads

Advanced

PPC (Pay-Per-Click)

Advertising

Advanced

HTML & CSS

Intermediate

Social Media Optimization

(SMO)

Advanced

Amazon Marketing

Canva & Figma

Advanced Advanced

SEO and Keyword Research

Advanced

SemRush

Advanced

WordPress Development

Advanced

Infographics, Video & Photo

**Editing** 

Advanced

## LANGUAGES

Konkani Fluent Hindi Fluent

Marathi Basic English Fluent